Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office records, 1922-2004.
New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office records, 1922-2004.
23-11-4061
New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office.
11 cubic feet.
Correspondence
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence from alumni and alumnae.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence from alumni and alumnae.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Human Ecology.; Cornell University -- Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University -- Students.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Boxes 1, 2 (the exception is records of deceased alumni are open for research) and 10 are restricted to permission of the office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Abercrombie, Elizabeth Roger, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Aberle, Helen A, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Adami, Virginia, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Adams, Ann Babcock, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Adams, Beverley Collins, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Adams, Elaine Ogle, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Adams, Grace Krieger, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Adams, Isabelle Pellegrino, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Adams, Marguerite H., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Adams, Olive Redmond, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Adie, Margaret Valele, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Ahl, Sandra Perrott, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Ainquist, Norma Hoagland, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Alden, Ann Bucholz, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Aines, Philip, 1951 (Box 11)
- Algeo, Virginia Liptay, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Ali, Zahida Amjad GR (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Allen, Dorothy Davis, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Allen, Jewelle Carlson, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Allen, Judith K., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Allen, Marcia Lee, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Allen, Sally, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Allen, Virginia, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Allessandrini, Norma, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Allison, Annette GR (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Allen, Shirley, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Alpert, Rosalyn (Shapero), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Alt, Elizabeth, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Altman, Patricia (Michaels), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Altman, Patricia (Michaels) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Altman, Patricia (Michaels) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Altman, Patricia (Michaels) (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Altman, Patricia (Michaels) (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Altman, Patricia (Michaels) (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Ambler, Ruth, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Ambry, Margaret MS, PhD, 1972, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Ames,Beth, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Ammarell, Mary E, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Andersen, Charlotte (Swanger), 1942 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Andersen, Mai Jean E., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Anderson, Elizabeth Sadd, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Anderson, Evelyn (Weber), 1940 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Anderson, Helen Jean, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Anderson, Mary Louise, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Anderson, Patricia Wehman, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Anderson, Ruth Sherlock GR (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Anderssen, Ella (Gleim) BS, MS, 1938, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Andrews, Ellen, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Angell, Lucia M., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Ansley, Ellen, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Antell, Marquerite Hannan, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Anwar, Pari, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Apeseche, Ruth Roeder, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Appiqnani, Georgianna, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Appleby, Sadye ms, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Arata, Dorothy GR (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Archibald, Marcia, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Armstrong, Helen E., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Armstrong, Marjorie MS, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Arnold, Eugene, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Arnold, Jean Allanson, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Arnold, Laura DuBois, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Aron, Joshua T., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Aronson, Natalie, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Arther, Barbara J., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Arthur, Laura, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Artman, Esther, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Arundel, Hope Mason, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Ashley, Joyce, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Astles, Mary (Brundage), 1940 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Atkins, Judith, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Atkinson, Sylvia Small, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Atteridg, Louise Van Nederyne, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Atteridg, Louise, 1948 (Box 11)
- Atwell, Jean MS, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Avety, Donna Jean, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Axinn, Nancy Wingsten, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Babcock, Celia E., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Babcock, Mildred MA, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Bachman, Betty Bloom, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Backaleiuck, Theda, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bacon, Janet Ostrander, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Baer, Jane, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bailey, Barbara (Clark), 1939 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Bailey, Eleanor, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Bailey, Francis (Crossman), 1930 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Baker, Virginia (Lowe), 1945 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Baker, Winifred, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Bald, Liddell, 1952 (Box 11)
- Baldwin, Margaret (Maxwell), 1942 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Ball, Alice Schilling, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Ball, Kathryn, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Balsizer, Leota GR, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Barber, June Norris, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Bardewyck, Loretta H. GR, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Barell, Elizabeth Ferguson, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Barlow, Elizabeth, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Barnes, Barbara GR (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Barnes, Eunice Shepard, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Barnett, Jacqueline, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Baron, M Virginia (Wilson) MS, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Barrett, Jane Hall, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Barron, Marjorie (Knapp), 1946 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Barstow, Beth, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Bartels, Constance Ruderisch, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Bartholomew, Ruth, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Bartlett, Nancy Garber, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Bartter, Scharlie Watson, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Bascom, Ruth (Fenton) MS, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Bassett, Barbara Beyrent, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Bassette, Elizabeth, 1934 (Box 11)
- Bates, Barbara Zimmerman, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Baum, Carol, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Baxter, Priscilla Coffin, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Bayer, Barbara A., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Bayern, Dorothy, 1951 (Box 11)
- Beall, Molly GR (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Bean, Marion, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Beasley, Eleanor (Beach), 1946 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Beatman, Thelma, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Beaudoin, Rachel, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Becker, Gloria (Spitz), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Becker, Harriet (Howell), 1941 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Becker, Harriet Howell, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Becker, Lois Myers, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Beckhorn, Verna, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Behrle, Fred GR (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Behrman, Patricia, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Beiderbecke, Evelyn, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Belden, Joan (Weisberg), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Belden, Kathryn (Kammerer), 1932 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Belinger, Gladys GR (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Belinke, Catherine GR (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Bell, Claire Naughton GR (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Bell, Dorothy (Reynolds), 1941 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Bell, Dorothy Lawrence, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Bellamy, Janet, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Bellamy, Janet Peifer, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Bellis, Roberta, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Bemis, Ann Sheridan, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Benedict, Walter, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Benko, Jane, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Bennett, Eileen, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Bennett, Elizabeth (Stevenson) BS, MS, 1937, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Bennett, Evelyn Willis, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Benson, Bonita J., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Berg, Adrian Pearsall, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Berg, Jerry Backus, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Berglund, Gladys (Winters), 1936 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Bergren, Joan (Mungeer), 1947 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Bergrun, Claire (Michaelson), 1943 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Berk, Ann Fox, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Berkenblit, Sarita Daniels, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Bernhard, Eleanor Norris, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bernhardt, Harriet Pflaum, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Bernstein, Anna-Rose, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bersohn, Birginia (Strauss), 1957 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Beyer, Virginia I. FR (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Bhagat, Shantilal GR, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Bharucha, Roshan P. GR (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Bickford, Edith (Messinger), 1919 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Bier, Martha (Signor), 1924 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Bigalow, June Woolever Steele, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Bill Greene - 1977 Recognition Project, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Binder, Bruce, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Binder, Jean, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Binger, Dianne (Nelson), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Biorn-Hausen, Vera, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Birkland, Barbara, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Bishop, Mary Kabat, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Bissell, Anna (Thomas), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Bizal, Rachel Sanders GR (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Bjorklund, Helen MS, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Black, Elizabeth (Kerr), 1943 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Black, Gladys M, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Black, Marilyn, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Black, Ruth C. (Pratt), 1926 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Blackburn, Gern (Bentley), 1938 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Blaisdell, Jane Edmonds, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Blanchard, Anne, 1952 (Box 11)
- Blank, Dorothy, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Blatchley, Alice (Pitcher), 1939 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Blatchley, Alice Pitcher, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Blazer, Arlene, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Block, Betty Carpenter, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Block, Marjorie E., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Blocker, Deborah, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Bloetjes, Mary K. PhD, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Bloodgood, Doris, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Bloodgood, Patricia (Hoagland), 1947 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Bloom, Lillian D., 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Bloomer, Miriam D., 1930 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Blum, Abraham H. PhD, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Blume, Fran deSylva, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Blumoff, Henrietta, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Bly, Helene Lingel, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Board, Elizabeth (Rogers), 1945 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Boardurau, Peggy, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Boardwan, Agnes, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Bocworth, Phylliis, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Boegly, Carolyn O. (Box 3, Folder 71)
  Faculty member
- Boehlecke, Olive (Griffin) MS, 1934, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Boettke, Eleanor, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Bohmont, Marilyn (Horn), 1946 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Bohnet, Mildred, 1943 (Box 11)
- Boicourt, Ruth Closson GR (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Boicourt, Ruth Closson MS, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Bokman, Mary Lou F!ynn, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bolden, Jeanne, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Bolton, Marie, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bonta, Helene J., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Booke, Norma Wilcox MS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Borchard, Sara, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Borchers, Mary Jane Sterner, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Borgman, Bernice GR (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Boroughs, Euphemia C. (Deade), 1946 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Borsher, Ione (Koller), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Bosshardt, Joan, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Bosshardt, Joan Clifton, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Bostwick, Jean Soule, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Bottorff, Ann Nash, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Bourne, Betty, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bower, Barbara Phillips, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Bower, Catherine L., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Bowmaker, Barbara Collins, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Bowman, Betty 0., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Bowman, Betty Bain GR (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Bowman, Betty MS, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Bowman, Ronald N., 1960 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Bowman, Susan Schurig, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Boxer, Barbara Ann (Kirschbaum), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Boyd, Isabel K., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Boyd, Rachel E., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Boylan, Elizabeth (Eddridge), 1937 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Boylan, Joseph Mary GR (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Boyle, Dorothy Scott, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Bradley, Janet (Hollowell), 1935 (Box 3, Folder 89)
- Bradt, Florence M., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bramley, Gertrude, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Brandford, Joanne (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Brandis, Mary Ellen, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Brandt, Henry GR (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Bratton, Esther (Crew) PhD, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Braun, Ellen B., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Braverman, Susan Plavin, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Brayton, Dorothy M., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Brereton, Elizabeth (Box 3, Folder 91)
- Brill, Hazel, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Brion, Ronnie, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Britting, Florence, 1952 (Box 11)
- Briukman, Janet Kennedy, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Broadhead, Mary Caryl, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Brodbeck, Rose F., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Brodie, Dvora R. '69, MBA, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 93)
- Brody, Marjorie (Rubin), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 94)
- Brody, Sonia B., 1956 (Box 3, Folder 95)
- Brody, Sonia Goldfarb, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bromberg, Ann Sherwin, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Bronfenbrenner, Urie (Box 3, Folder 97)
- Bronfenbrenner, Urie (Box 3, Folder 98)
- Bronfenbrenner, Urie (Box 3, Folder 99)
- Bronfenbrenner, Urie, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 96)
- Brooks, Mille, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Brooks, Virginia, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Brotman, Judith E., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Brougham, Helen, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Brown, Ann (Blodgett), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 100)
- Brown, Audrey, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Brown, Bonnie Simonson, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Brown, Carol Rasmussen, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Brown, Cornelia L. BS HE, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 101)
- Brown, Elizabeth BS, MS, 1940, 1945 (Box 11)
- Brown, Hannah (Blumenthal), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 102)
- Brown, Judith Kredel, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Brown, Marcia, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Brown, Marjorie (Chapman), 1933 (Box 3, Folder 103)
- Brown, Mary (Stenbuck), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 104)
- Brown, Meta Brammer, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Brown, Mina, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Brown, Muriel (Welch), 1947 (Box 3, Folder 105)
- Brown, Nancy, 1959 (Box 11)
- Brown, Pearl Woodruff, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Brownfield, Dorothy PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Bruce, Harriet Parshall, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Bruggeman, Fern M., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Brumsted, Evelyn, 1945 (Box 11)
- Brundage, Mary Elizabeth, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bryce, Theodora MA, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Buck, David M, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 106)
- Buckley, Muriel Cabot MS Ed, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Bugg, Winona (Brower), 1943 (Box 3, Folder 107)
- Bull, Anne C., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bull, Margaret, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Bundy, Peggy, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Burch, Anita (Bishansky), 1963 (Box 3, Folder 108)
- Burch, Lois Wood, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Burgess, Constance GR (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Burke, Dorothy, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Burke, Joyce E., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Burke, Phyllis (Colling), 1942 (Box 3, Folder 109)
- Burke, Rosalind Heath, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Burmaster, Rachel, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Burnett, Nancy (Milliman), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Burns, Mae Grimes, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 110)
- Burns, Winifred A., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Burr, Cornelia Clary MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Burroughs, Effie MS (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Burton, Catherine, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Burton, Mary (Clark), 1946 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Burton, Mary (McDorman) PhD, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Buschner, Carol Slocum, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Busekist, Edna E. GR (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Bush, Harold Jr. MNS, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Bushey, Esther (Murry), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 111)
- Buso, Mildred, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Bussanik, Bertha, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bussing, Marylou, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Butler, Mollie (Parker), 1940 (Box 3, Folder 112)
- Butler, Mollie Parker MS, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Butterfield, Ellen, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Butzine, Janet Smith, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Buyse, Barbara Sauer, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Buyske, Jo (Kessel), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Byers, Ruth (Gottshall), 1950 (Box 3, Folder 113)
- Bymers, Gwendolyn (Box 3, Folder 115)
- Bymers, Gwendolyn (Box 3, Folder 116)
- Bymers, Gwendolyn (Box 3, Folder 117)
- Bymers, Gwendolyn (Box 3, Folder 118)
- Bymers, Gwendolyn (Box 3, Folder 114)
- Byrd, Alease MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Byrd, Flossie GR (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Cadiz, Anita L, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 119)
- Cady, Helen J. (Box 3, Folder 120)
- Calby, Diana Heywood, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Calby, Joseph, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 121)
- Cameron, Jane Allison, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Campbell F. Elizabeth GR, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Campbell, Ada Marie GR (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Campbell, Anne (Hughes), 1942 (Box 3, Folder 122)
- Campbell, Marybelle (Dalton), 1927 (Box 3, Folder 123)
- Cancellieri, Grace, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Canoyer, Helen G. GR (Box 3, Folder 124)
- Canoyer, Helen G. GR (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Cantwell, Mary Jo GR, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 125)
- Caplin, Belle Kaufman, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Care, Eleanor, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Carlin, Agnes-Frances GR (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Carmon, Myra J., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Carnes, Gaynelle GR (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Caro, Gloria, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Carozza, Evelyn (Petzold), 1935 (Box 3, Folder 126)
- Carozza, Karen, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 127)
- Carpenter, Cliff, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 128)
- Carpenter, Elsie (Bjorkman), 1933 (Box 3, Folder 129)
- Carpenter, Norma Bosworth, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Carpenter, Pat, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Carpenter, Virginia GR (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Carroll, Helen MS, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 130)
- Carson, Mary, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Carter, Mary Meter, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Carver, Audrey H., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 131)
- Case, Emma (Mammel), 1934 (Box 3, Folder 132)
- Case, Margery, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Case, Marguerite GR (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Caspar, Mila, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Caster, Bethel, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 133)
- Castle, Mary, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Castor, Doris Strong, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Caulum, Vera A. MS, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Chachkes, Sandra, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Chadwick, Helen (Reichert), 1938 (Box 3, Folder 134)
- Chakpitak, Saovanee Sudsanel GR (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Chamberlain, Barbara, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Chamberlain, Elizabeth (Peet), 1941 (Box 3, Folder 135)
- Chamberlain, Leah, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 136)
- Chamberlain, Nancy Allen, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Chandler, Patricia (Smalley), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 137)
- Chapman, Barbara, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Chase, Elizabeth A., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Chase, Merle Roat, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Chauvin, Margaret, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Chen, Helen GR (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Cheney, Martha (Atwood), 1940 (Box 3, Folder 138)
- Chepus, Elizabeth Bastian GR (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Chiron, Blanche Zimet, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Chollet, Janet Dingwall, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Christensen, Charlotte, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 139)
- Christensen, Janet Reid, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Christensen, Janeth (Reid), 1947 (Box 3, Folder 140)
- Christiana, Margaret (Soper), 1940 (Box 3, Folder 141)
- Christiana, Margaret Soper, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cima, Joyce W., 1952 (Box 3, Folder 142)
- Cladel, Mabel M., 1935 (Box 3, Folder 143)
- Clark, Barbara Ann, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Clark, Beverly Benz, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Clark, Dorothy Cooper, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Clark, Esther, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Clark, Regina (Box 3, Folder 144)
- Clark, Sally Lou, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Clark, Shirley E., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Clarke, Elsie Strum, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Classen, Lynn (Engelsman), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 145)
- Classon, Dorothy (Jacobson), 1941 (Box 3, Folder 146)
- Clement, Jane, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Clipp, Elizabeth (Colerick) (Box 3, Folder 147)
- Clist, Mary (Pollard), 1944 (Box 3, Folder 148)
- Cloflin, Helen, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Cloney, Kaisa Karikka, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Coble, Mary Catherine, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Cockefair, Mary Louisae GR (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Cocking, Rodney, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 149)
- Cockram, Martha (Benning) (Box 3, Folder 150)
- Codling, Nancy, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Cohen, Amy (Goldman), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 151)
- Cohen, Lois Leeds, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cohen, Lola Rose, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Cohen, Ruth (Theiberger), 1947 (Box 3, Folder 152)
- Cole, Jean, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 153)
- Cole, Mary (Myers), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 154)
- Coleman, Jason Pinckney, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Colgrove, Mary C. MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Collection for Bill Greene Book (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Collins, Betty GR (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Collins, Patricia GR (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Collins, Patricia MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Compton, Eunice Morris, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Conley, Irene, 1946 (Box 11)
- Conlon, Constance Salm, 1955 (Box 11)
- Connelly, Loula MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Connelly, Loula MS, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 155)
- Connelly, Rita GR (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Conner, Margaret (Sturm), 1935 (Box 3, Folder 156)
- Connolly, Dorothy, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Connor, Virginia Pease, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Conrath, Dora (Wagner), 1930 (Box 3, Folder 157)
- Conrath, Dora (Wagner) (Box 3, Folder 158)
- Conrath, Dora (Wagner) (Box 3, Folder 159)
- Conrath, Dora (Wagner) (Box 3, Folder 160)
- Conrath, Dora (Wagner) (Box 3, Folder 161)
- Contant, Beatrice (O'Brien), 1946 (Box 3, Folder 162)
- Conti, Dorothy, 1943 (Box 11)
- Cook, Alma L, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cook, Alma L., 1940 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Cook, Ruth GR (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Cooper, Frances (Otto), 1938 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Cope, Ann (Reeves), 1941 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Cope, Ann Reeves, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Cope, Patricia (Speidel), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Cope, Patricia Speidel, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Copeland, Nancy, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Corcoran, Esther, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Corcoran, Jeanne M., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Corey, Ann, 1939 (Box 1)
- Cornell, Muriel Meshman, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Cornish, Elizabeth Turmey, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cornish, Rosalie, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Cornwall, Elizabeth, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Correll, Rosemary (Pew), 1944 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Correll, Rosemary Pew, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Corsey, Michele W., 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Cosgrove, Hannah Gottshall, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Costick, Evelyn Corwith, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cothran, Dorothy, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cothran, Ruth E., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Cottrell, Casper L., 1928 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Coultrap, Lucille F. GR (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Cousens, Dorothy MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Covell, Alice, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Coveney, Anne R. PhD, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Cowdery, Phyllis (DuBois), 1948 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Cox, Diane Martin, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Cox, Marion F., 1923 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Cox, Nancy, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Cox, Nancy (Lain), 1948 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Craig, Dave, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cramer, Betty, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Cravens, Louise Manley, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Crawford, Bernice GR (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Crawford, Elizabeth, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Crawford, Joan O'Herron, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Crawford, Laura, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Crispell, Judith (Banton) MS, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Cronk, Alice (Douglass), 1944 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Crosby, Grace (Johnson), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Crowe, Natalie (Dunn) MS, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Crum, Helen, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Cuddy, Roberta (Harvey), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Cudworth, Marian, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Cunard, Sherwyn MS, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Curry, Lala J. MS, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Curtis, Emma Rose, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Curtis, Jean, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Cutler, Virginia (Farrer), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Czajkowski, Janina M GR (Box 2, Folder 62)